[{"answer": " What for", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " He's a busy man", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "To tell the truth, ever since I found my natural callin' I done time in so many smal", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Well, ya know, my friend...  Doesn't it say so there", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'm not talking about my friend or my friend, buddy, what I'm talkin' about is that crummy meeting and what that nurse did to you", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Did to you and all the rest of you guys", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What for", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Lobotomy", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "After breakfast, my friend, after breakfast", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yes. Now run along like a good boy and see that you wash up properly", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " ", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What was it about her that disturbed you so, my friend", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend, were you afraid of her, or of her love", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "So why are you talking to him", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "It doesn't help him", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Bullshit. You ain't got no way out", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " ", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Now you talkin'", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Bet you ass..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "He's a patient, Rose..", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "They're sleeping, that place. They're sleeping. An' we gotta keep it down so we don't disturb their sleep", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Oh, no, that place. Not these loonies. These are nice guys. Nice guys", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Oh, no, that place. Not these loonies. These are nice guys. Nice guys", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What smell", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What's that smell", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Smells weird. Smells like pneumonia", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yes, Mister my friend", "docId": "oneflewover.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No. Mister my friend, that is not true", "qsentId": 32}]